<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:paddingBottom="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
    android:paddingLeft="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingRight="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingTop="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
    app:layout_behavior="@string/appbar_scrolling_view_behavior"
    tools:context="com.example.siddharth.christmas.ana2"
    tools:showIn="@layout/activity_ana22">
    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/hello_sid"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="UNIT-I             \n\nObject Oriented System Development: Understanding Object Oriented Development, Understanding Object Concepts, Benefits of Object Oriented Development.              \n\nJava Programming Fundamentals: Introduction. Overview of Java, Data Type, Variables and Arrays, Operators, Control statements, Classes, Methods , Inheritance, Packages and Interfaces.              \n\nUNIT-II              \n\nExceptions Handling, Multithreaded Programming, I/O basics, Reading Console input and output, Reading and Writing Files, Print Writer Class, String Handling.              \n\nUNIT-III              \n\nExploring Java Language, Collections Overview, Collections Interfaces, Collections Classes, Iterators, Random Access Interface, Maps, Comparators, Arrays, Legacy classes and interfaces, Sting tokenizer, BitSet, Date, Calendar, Timer.              \n\nUNIT-IV              \n\nIntroducing AWT working With Graphics: AWT Classes, Working with Graphics.              \n\nEvent Handling: Two Event Handling Mechanisms, The Delegation Event Model, Event Classes, Source of Events, Event Listener Interfaces.              \n\nAWT Controls: Control Fundamentals, Labels, Using Buttons, Applying Check Boxes, CheckboxGroup, Choice Controls, Using Lists, Managing Scroll Bars, Using TextField, Using TextArea, Understanding Layout Managers, Menu bars and Menus, Dialog Boxes, FileDialog, Handling events by Extending AWT Components, Exploring the controls, Menus and Layout Managers.              \n\nUNIT-V              \n\nJava I/O classes and interfaces, Files, Stream and Byte classes, Character Streams, Serialization.              \n\nSuggested Reading:              \n1.Herbert Schildt, The Complete Reference Java, 7th Edition, Tata McGraw Hill, 2005.              \n2.James M Slack, Programming and Problem solving with JAVA, Thomson Learning, 2002              \n3.C Thomas Wu, An Introduction to Object Oriented programming with Java, Tata McGraw Hill, 2005."
            android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceLarge"
            />
    </ScrollView>

</RelativeLayout>
